willowgarage.com 2015-12-29

# Willow Garage Privacy Policy | Willow Garage

**_This Privacy Policy was last updated in November 2008._**

Willow Garage, Inc. (“Willow Garage”, “we”, or “us”) takes the privacy and protection of personal information very seriously. By visiting and using the Sites and Services or by registering for the Services and creating an Account, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”). Unless otherwise defined herein, capitalized terms shall have the meanings assigned to such terms in the Willow Garage Terms of Use that you can find at http://www.willowgarage.com/pages/TermsOfUse and which incorporate this Privacy Policy by reference.

 **What This Privacy Policy Covers**

This Privacy Policy describes Willow Garage’s practices with respect to Personal Information and Anonymous Information that we collect when you use the Services. This Privacy Policy does not apply to the use of your Personal Information that is collected by third parties that Willow Garage does not own or control or that do not support Willow Garage in providing the Services.

“Personal Information” is information that is personally identifiable like names, addresses, e-mail addresses, or phone numbers, as well as other non-public information that is associated with the foregoing.

“Anonymous Information” means information that is not associated with or linked to your Personal Information; Anonymous Information does not permit the identification of individual persons. 

We collect and use Personal Information and Anonymous Information as described in this Privacy Policy from Users.

BY USING THE SERVICES OR SUBMITTING PERSONAL INFORMATION THROUGH THE SERVICES, YOU EXPRESSLY CONSENT TO THE PROCESSING OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION ACCORDING TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY.

YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION MAY BE PROCESSED IN THE COUNTRY WHERE IT WAS COLLECTED AS WELL AS OTHER COUNTRIES (INCLUDING THE UNITED STATES) WHERE LAWS REGARDING PROCESSING OF PERSONAL INFORMATION MAY BE LESS STRINGENT THAN THE LAWS IN YOUR COUNTRY AND BY USING THE SERVICES OR SUBMITTING PERSONAL INFORMATION THROUGH THE SERVICES, YOU ARE EXPRESSLY CONSENTING TO SUCH PROCESSING.

 **Personal Information We Collect**

We collect the following Personal Information that you submit to us voluntarily:

• If you register for the Services and create an Account to become a Member, we collect your name, a username, your e-mail address, and a password for your Account.  
• When you register for the Services we may also collect additional information on an optional basis, including, but not limited to, the city, state, and country where you live, and the company you work for.  
• When you contact us by sending us an e-mail, we will collect any information that is contained in (and/or attached to) your e-mail.  
• When you apply for a job at Willow Garage, we collect any information that you send to us in connection with your application.

 **Personal Information Collected Via Technology**

As you use the Services, certain information may also be collected passively, including your Internet protocol (IP) address and the browser that you use to visit the Sites. Willow Garage also stores a small text file called a “Cookie” on your computer to store your login information (if any) and your personal preferences for the Services. Willow Garage may use both session Cookies (which expire once you close your web browser) and persistent Cookies (which stay on your computer until you delete them). While you will still be able to use the Services if you disable Cookies in your browser, certain parts of the Services may not function as effectively.

Since the foregoing information may be collected when you are signed into the Services, this information may be associated by us with Personal Information that we have collected from you.  
 **  
Personal Information From Other Sources**

We may receive Personal Information about you from outside the Sites, such as telephone, fax, mail, or from third parties that provide services for us that are related to the Services. We may add this information to the information we have already collected from you via the Services.  
 **  
Use Of Information We Collect**

In general, information (including Personal Information) you submit to us, or to third parties that support us in collecting information, is used by us to provide you and others with the Services, to respond to requests that you make, to improve our Services and to better tailor the features, performance and support of the Services.

We may also use your Personal Information to provide you with notifications related to your use of the Services, such as electronic newsletters or promotional e-mails, should you request to receive such communications from us.

We may create Anonymous Information records from Personal Information by excluding information (such as your name) that makes the information personally identifiable to you. We may also create Anonymous Information on how you use the Services. We may use this Anonymous Information for internal purposes, such as analyzing usage patterns so that we may enhance the Services, and we also reserve the right to use and disclose any Anonymous Information at our discretion.

 **Feedback**

If you provide feedback about the Services to us, we may use and disclose such feedback for any purpose, provided we do not associate such feedback with your Personal Information. We will collect any information contained in such feedback and will treat the Personal Information in it in accordance with this Privacy Policy.  
Disclosure of Personal Information  
Except as otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy, we do not disclose to or share your Personal Information with third parties, unless you ask or authorize us to do so. 

We may provide your Personal Information to third party service providers and suppliers who work on behalf of or with us to provide you with some of the services and features of the Services and to help us communicate with our Users. However, these service providers and suppliers do not have any independent right to use this information except to help us provide the Services.

Although we currently do not have a parent company, any subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under a common control (collectively, “Affiliates”), we may in the future. We may share some or all of your Personal Information with these Affiliates, in which case we will require our Affiliates to honor this Privacy Policy.

In the event Willow Garage goes through a business transition such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your Personal Information will likely be among the assets transferred. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Willow Garage or its assets may continue to use your Personal Information as set forth in this Privacy Policy. You hereby consent to Willow Garage sharing your Personal Information under the above circumstances.

We may (and you authorize us to) disclose information we have collected from and about you (including Personal Information) if we believe in good faith that such disclosure is necessary to (a) comply with relevant laws or to respond to subpoenas or warrants served on us; (b) to enforce any agreement we may have entered into with you and to enforce the Privacy Policy; or (c) to protect and defend the rights or property of us, other Users, or third parties.

 **Choices Regarding Personal Information**

We will include unsubscribe instructions in each newsletter or promotional communication you receive from us.

We may send you service-related announcements (such as, but not limited to, notice that we have changed the Services, the Terms of Use, or the Privacy Policy) when we believe it is necessary to do so. You may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature, but if you do not wish to receive these announcements, you have the option to terminate the Account you may have with us. You understand that any termination of your Account may involve deletion of your Account information (and associated Content) from our live databases and all the information and data stored for such Account in the Services. Willow Garage will not have any liability whatsoever to you for any termination of your account or related deletion of you information. 

When we delete information that we have collected from or about you, it will be deleted from our active databases but may remain in our archives.

 **Links to Other Web Sites**

The Services may contain links to other web sites that are not owned or controlled by Willow Garage. The provision of such links is for your convenience and does not signify our endorsement of such web sites or location or its contents. We have no control over, do not review and are not responsible for the privacy policies of or content displayed on such other web sites. Please be aware that the terms of the Privacy Policy do not apply to any outside web sites.

 **Privacy of Minors**

We do not intentionally collect or maintain information from persons under the age of 13.  
 **  
Security and Confidentiality**

Willow Garage has put in place commercially reasonable and appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. However, no company, including Willow Garage, can fully eliminate security risks associated with Personal Information. 

**Changes in this Privacy Policy**

As part of the Terms of Use, this Privacy Policy is subject to occasional amendment, in accordance with the terms of the Terms of Use.

 **Contact Us**

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our Privacy Policy please contact us by sending us an e-mail to [privacy@willowgarage.com](mailto:privacy@willowgarage.com)
